[{"answer": "Well, quite clearly that they have enough information to focus on these individuals as suspects, not just persons of interest, but suspects.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "If you were wearing your commissioner hat, what would you read into what the FBI has done today?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "You can guarantee they know more, they have much more video than they're putting out to the public.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Would that be your deduction?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I won't even speculate on that because it would be useless speculation at this stage of the game.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is your gut feeling that these two suspects are still around or that they would have disappeared at fast as possible?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, it depends.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "So is it likely from your experience that people that go to that length of planning and preparing and executing, would they normally have some kind of escape route, do you think?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think much credit should be given to the law enforcement generally.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What is your take on where we are with this investigation?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Yes, Piers, this is the reason that we didn't hear this before now, that premature leak yesterday may have impacted the investigation as they say, with unintended consequences.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "When they release pictures and video like this, is it safe to assume that all their decks are in a row in the sense of clearly once this goes public, these two characters will know that they're on to them, will by then they have cleared everything with the ports and the airports and so on so if they try and make a run for it to get out of the country, they're ready for them?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Do you think, as my other guests have implied tonight, that they have a lot more information they're not releasing?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "What you're seeing is the actual videos.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Working on that, do you think the FBI again may have a better idea than we do just from what's released?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, apparently they're being absolutely inundated both to their websites, also e-mails, calls, everything, and social media is erupting with information.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Also, part of what they're looking to now do by pushing these images out, everybody who was in that area guaranteed is now checking their videos, checking their photos to see, did I actually catch these two guys on my video?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "He's still in critical condition.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What is his condition today?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I don't want to speculate, but you know, I knew something was wrong.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "I mean, do you think that if you hadn't been there to do what you did when you did it, that he may not be alive today?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "You know, I don't -- I hope they get them, you know.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "And what has been your reaction to the release of the pictures by the FBI of the two suspects?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What do you make of the development today with the two suspects given that it clearly shows a team?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, the jury is still out.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do we know any more about who is more likely to have done this, homegrown or a foreign, perhaps al Qaeda related cell?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "No, you know, Piers, I think they've been very deliberate about letting -- leaving all those options open, right, because what's really important to them is to find the individuals and once you've got them, you'll know -- for certain what the motivation was.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "In other words, does the FBI know a bit more and perhaps believe it may be homegrown for that reason, or are they thinking perhaps no, this is looking more and more like al Qaeda?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "You're absolutely right, Piers.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Is that what today is all about, that they need to have people coming on saying I know who these are?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "It would be extremely easy.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Jim Maxwell, looking at this device here, how easy is it for a would-be terrorist to bring this kind of thing on a backpack into a situation like this?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Is that how they would have done it?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Well, it could go in several different directions.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "The fact that they stayed around to see the explosions, what does that tell you about potentially the kind of construct of this device?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Fran Townsend, in terms of the international element to this, if it is a foreign group related to al Qaeda or whatever, and they have either absconded or are trying to abscond the country, what are the wheels that go into motion there as far as national security?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "They'll get cooperation.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What kind of cooperation can the FBI expect from places like Pakistan?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "It tells me that somebody had some practice here, and somebody cased the area.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "What does that tell you?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "I would be worried about it, but it was a great move today by putting their faces on television, as was said earlier by Fran.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "If you were running the FBI with this, how worried would you be that you may never track them down?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Doing fine.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Lisa, first of all, how are you feeling?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Oh, I was watching TV.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What did you think was happening?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "She -- yeah, she has some scratches on her eyes.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "In terms of the injuries that Lisa suffered, it's all from the glass, is it?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I was just lucky.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you feel fortunate that your injuries aren't as bad as so many others?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Last I heard, our uncle wasn't able to go to his house.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Are any of the families allowed to go anywhere near it?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, you know, talking about the blast first, Piers, and putting this in some context with respect to Boston, because you and I were talking about this last night.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What is the state of play there now with all those different things?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "It was -- first of all, it was an honor to be able to be there, given the light of the unfortunate situation.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "What was it like to be there?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I'm just happy that they are finally getting somewhere.", "docId": "130418pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "When you saw that breaking this afternoon, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 443}]